senvideo.com 2010-06-21

# SenVideo

SenVideo values the privacy of its users, visitors and customers who access the services provided through www.senvideo.com. This Privacy Notice is incorporated into and is subject to the SenVideo Terms of Use. Your use of the this site and any personal information you provide on SenVideo remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Notice and our Terms of Use. SenVideo provides this Privacy Notice to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using this site Please note that any video, image, or other content posted at the direction of Users onto the SenVideo website becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Notice.

Collected information:  
You provide certain personally identifiable information (name, email address, etc) to SenVideo when choosing to participate in various activities on this website such as uploading videos, posting messages in our forums or in the video comments section, voting on polls, using the chat system 

Log file informatiom:  
When you use the SenVideo website, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These may include the following: web request, Internet Protocol, address, browser type, browser language, referring or exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

Cookies Information:   
When you visit the SenVideo website, we may send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. SenVideo uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Senvideo website may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. 

User Information:  
If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the SenVideo website, then we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the senVideo website. 

Other:  
Any personal information or video content that you publicly and voluntarily disclose online becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your account name and not your email address is displayed to other Users when you upload videos or send messages through the SenVideo website and other Users can contact you through messages and comments. Any videos that you submit to the SenVideo website and set as public may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. SenVideo do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes for example to notify you of major SenVideo website changes or service change SenVideo may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws.

SenVideo also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally identifiable information that SenVideo believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our web site, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of SenVideo, our Users or others. 

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the SenVideo website, in which case we may not be able to provide certain services to you.

You may update or correct your personal profile information and email preferences at any time by visiting your account profile page. Media files uploaded by Users to the SenVideo website cannot be removed and remain subject to our Terms of Use.

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps such as requesting a unique password to verify your identity before granting you profile access or making corrections. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times.

Please contact SenVideo with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice, your personal information, your consent, or your opt-in or opt-out choices using our contact form.

SenVideo allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the SenVideo website. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the SenVideo website. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (cookies, JavaScript, etc) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see.

If SenVideo learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. 

This Privacy Notice may be revised periodically and this will be reflected by the effective date below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. Your continued use of the SenVideo webite constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Notice and any future revisions.

last modified April 30, 2007  
\-------------------------------------  
Please contact SenVideo with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice
